原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译     AlgerDestiny  VeadCool  A序列
翻译     克里斯托  二糯米  不见侠  五天
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     西·查
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第十四集
春田镇古戈尔普勒克斯剧院
现在我  奇诺斯  终于拥有了世界末日软件
Now that I, Chinnos, finally wield the Doomsday App,
我可以让星球浴火重生
I can restart this planet in flames,
如同乌托邦
as a utopia.
说不好啊奇诺斯  你说"乌托邦"
I don't know, Chinnos. You say "utopia,"
我听到的是"杀光所有人"
but what I'm hearing is "kill everyone."
而我真的不想再找个新的干洗店
And I really don't want to find a new dry cleaner.
你的好笑却不够好笑的玩笑
Your funny-but-not-too-funny banter
不会拯救你的  镁镁侠
will not save you, Magnesium Man.
但它的确分散了你的注意力对吧  怪老爹
Yeah, but it did distract you, didn't it, Dad Bod?
拿下他  空射侠
Take him, Airshot!
上啊空射侠  用空气枪
Yes, Airshot, pump that air gun!
他抽了五下  想想那是什么样的压力
Five pumps? Think of the pressure.
怎么了嘛  头疼日
Aw, what's the matter? Bad head day?
是时候该把守护者踢出去了
It's time I took the Vindicators out of the equation.
重启
我现在接受你的邀舞
I'll take that dance now.
他们的初吻是他们的最后一吻
Their first kiss was their last.
未完待续
原来它叫水晶之战
It was called Crystal War
是因为他们都变成了水晶
because they were all turned to crystals.
现在不是你做冷酷的分析的时候
Hey, now is not the time for your cold-hearted analysis.
续集明年才出
The sequel isn't coming out for a year.
是何等慈爱的上帝才会让我们等这么久
What loving God would make us wait that long?
一年  就像万年一样啊
A year? That's, like, a million years.
我可等不了  不准丢下我
I cannot wait. Don't you leave me,
你这穿斗篷的讨厌鬼
you be-cape-ed gob-smashers!
11个月以后
春田小学
孩子们  我今天把你们调离课堂
Children, I pulled you out of your classes today
是为了警告你们一种新型网络潮流
to warn you of a dangerous new Internet trend.
红灯笼辣椒挑战
The paprika challenge?
八号球挑战
The eight ball challenge?
不  我要说的遭火热模仿的特技
No, the highly-imitatable stunt I'm referring to
西摩的屏保
是"人体升旗"挑战
is the "flag yourself" challenge.
仅仅口头警告是不够的
Instead of a merely verbal warning,
我明白更具威慑力的是
it's clear to me a more effective deterrent
将这个特技的视频展示给你们看
would be to show you a video of the stunt
由油管网红响应侠表演示范
performed by YouTube star Reaction Guy.
响应侠
Whoa, Reaction Guy?
所有人都是受他号召才响应的
Everybody who's anybody gets reacted to by him.
好好看  学着  别这么干
Watch and learn... to not do this.
咋地了  响应行动  我是你们的响应侠
What up, Reaction Faction? It's your boy, Reaction Guy.
今天我要响应"人体升旗挑战"
Today I'm gonna be reacting to the Flag Yourself Challenge.
向我的队友打招呼  刺猬  瘦薄荷  白酋长
Shout-out to my crew, Hedgehog, Thin Mint, and White Malik.
他们会像升旗一样把我升起来
They're gonna raise me like a flag.
紧张刺激
this is so clench!
已响应
酷啊
Wow, cool!
五分钟后
各位  我是巴仔·辛普森
Hey, guys, this is Bart Simpson
这是我的新频道  响应巴仔
from my new channel, Reaction Bart.
大声向我的朋友白西摩问好  他向我宣传了
Big shout-out to my boy White Seymour for putting me onto
"人体升旗挑战"  紧张刺激
the Flag Yourself Challenge. So clench!
无尽战争的退伍老兵
好了  开始吧  等着瞧
Okay, hit it. Check it out.
我在向我的黑子们挥手  他们压根都不知道
I'm waving at my haters and they don't even know it.
紧迫  紧迫
Clench! Clench!
买我的大麻
Buy my merch.
即将推出大麻  大麻
Merch to come. Merch!
他的腹斜肌一定撕裂了
His obliques must be shredded.
下次去游泳的时候我一定要好好看看
I got to check them out next time we go swimming.
苗浩斯  不
Milhouse, no!
我需要你输入密码上传视频
I need your passcode to upload the video.
春田综合医院
此处重复利用用过的创可贴
苗浩斯  我在礼品店给你买了气球
Yo, Milhouse, I got you a balloon form the gift shop.
是女孩
你是男孩
医生怎么说
So what'd the doctors say?
全身扭伤
I have a full-body sprain.
大部分肌肉都错位到其他骨头上去了
Most of my muscles are wrapped around the wrong bones.
好了  小勇士  理疗时间到
Okay, champ, physical therapy time.
准备好练四小时的弹力带了吗
Who's ready for four hours of stretch bands?
不  不要用紫色的
No, not the purple.
葡萄糖
Glucose?
我随便"躺"了不要介意
Don't mind if I do-cose.
好了  哥们  你可以的
Okay, mate, you can do this.
很困难  但是小家伙们还指望着你呢
It's hard, but those little buggers are counting on you.
为了小家伙们
Do it for the buggers.
大美妞们你们好啊
Top of the bing-bong, ladies.
-你是格伦·丹吉尔  -你是空射侠
- You're Glen Tangier. - You're Airshot.
你们好啊  医护小天使们
Good on you, Nightingales.
谁能给我指个路  我找
Now, who can point me towards, uh,
苗浩斯·范浩腾
"Milhouse Van Houten"?
走廊尽头左手边那间  格林
Ooh, right down the hall and to the left, Glen.
这么会撩  黛比
Flirt much, Debby?
抱歉  我们不能都和
Sorry, we can't all be married to
奥格登维尔汽车美容大拿优选公爵结婚吧
Ogdenville's car detailing king Duke Druthers.
怎么样  小兄弟
What's up, little bro?
我现实里最爱的超级英雄怎么样了
How's my favorite real-life superhero?
天呐  你是格伦·丹吉尔
Holy crap, you're Glen Tangier.
从来没听说过他
Never heard of him.
我的身份是空射侠
The name's Airshot.
你是我最爱的守护者
You're my favorite Vindicator.
你不掌控其它力量  只擅长玩空气
You don't even have any powers, you're just super good at air.
放轻松  别太激动  苗浩斯
Uh, easy now. Don't get too excited, Milhouse.
我不是
Oh, I'm not...
我是苗浩斯
I am Milhouse.
没错了  放轻松  英雄
That's right. Calm down, hero.
别让你自己的状况更糟
Don't make whatever you have worse.
情况开始恶化了吗  不要跟我说恶化了
Is it something that gets worse? Please don't say it gets worse.
别担心  空射侠  我没事
Oh, don't worry, Airshot, I'm okay.
你是不是鼓起勇气了呢
Well, aren't you just Pimm to the brim with Adelaide spunk?
谢天谢地
Oh, thank boomerang Jesus
你不是那些勇敢的小家伙
you're not one of those brave little buggers
我不必让你看这个
that I have to show this to.
等下  你那里面装的是什么
Wait, what do you got in there?
这是一台装有续集的笔记本电脑
Oh, it's a laptop with the sequel
《守护者联盟  水晶垃圾》
to the Vindicators: Crystal garbage.
只要你没事就好  兄弟
All that matters is you're gonna be okay, mate.
反正我也不想做演员
Never wanted to be an actor anyway,
应该像我爸一样做个考拉屠夫
just a simple koala butcher like me old man.
空射侠  格伦
Yo, Airshot. Glen.
漫宝影业版权所有
保密文件
用户登录请验证
好啊
Hello.
《守护者联盟  水晶战争2  复活》
我的个老天
Sweet boomerang Jeebus.
多好的结局啊
What an ending.
大家看到这个结局会崩溃的
People are gonna freak out when they see it...
还得等到一个月之后
in a month from now.
在上映之前我是唯一知道电影情节的人
Till then, I'm the only one that knows what happens.
只有我知道
Only I know.
我是这个世界上有力量的小孩
I'm the most powerful kid in the world.
把袋鼠腿扔进沸水里
Toss that Kanga shank into the billy-boil.
在无限跳跃[游戏术语]的时候肉会软下来的
It'll be tender by moon jump.
请勿高调入内
肥神  我看完了《守护者联盟  水晶战争2》
Yo, Fat Thor, I've seen Vindicators: Crystal War 2.
-你真敢吹  -我的兄弟空射侠给我看过了
- You blaspheme! - My buddy Airshot showed it to me.
是吗  是吗
Ha. I repeat, ha.
澳大利亚的一个州
就好像塔斯马尼亚美男子格伦·丹吉尔这种人
As if Glen Tangier, the Tasmanian Adonis,
会屈尊跟你这种人打交道
would deign to interact with someone of your insignificance.
你输了  守护者
You are defeated, Vindicator.
你忘了我还能呼吸
Not as long as I'm still breathing.
我的个老天爷  然后呢
Sweet batarang Jesus. Tell me more.
免费试看已结束
The first taste was free,
继续请付费
the next is gonna cost you.
我盯那本《凌晨三点博士》漫画很久了
I've had my eye on that Dr. 3 A.M. graphic novel.
做好准备  故事的发展是
Okay, strap yourself in. The way it goes down is...
先等等  你将要说的话
But pause. The knowledge you offer
会剧透本年度盛事电影
would spoil the movie event of the year.
不  本世纪
Nay, century.
不  本时代
Nay, epoch.
不  所有夏天
Nay, summer.
一个字也别说了
Tell me nothing.
但我快被好奇心吞噬了
Ah, but my curiosity consumes me.
那好我接着说  电影开头的标志是...
All right, here's the deal, the movie starts on the logo...
闭嘴
Silence!
你说
Speak!
别说了
Speak not.
详细点
Expound!
我通过了考验  我可以
I pass the test. I will diminish
无欲无求做回漫画男
and remain Comic Book Guy.
哦  虾
Ooh, shrimp.
你愿意为拒绝知道剧情付出什么代价
What would you give me not to find out what happens?
滚吧  剧透小子
Be gone, Spoiler Boy.
剧透小子
Spoiler Boy.
我喜欢
I like that.
就是他看了守护者联盟 水晶战争2 复活
That's the kid who saw Vindicators: Crystal War 2: Resurgence.
听他话不然会被剧透
Do what he says or he'll spoil the ending.
我必须守护耳朵的处女听
I must protect my virgin ears.
我觉得还能再来点
I think you can do better than that.
每人四个鸡块
Four chicken lumpettes per person.
即使这个人知道是哪个守护者在对抗
Even if that person knows which Vindicator
空手道蝎子时用去了大家三分之一的力量吗
loses a third of their powers fighting Karate Scorpion?
闭嘴  这电影在两元影院上映后
Zip it. My boyfriend's taking me to see that movie
首轮电影下档后  以折扣价格放映
我男朋友会带我看
when it gets to the two-dollar theater.
取消午餐
辛普森  你每多吃一块鸡块
Simpson, you're getting one day of detention
就多留校一天
for every extra lumpette you eat.
留校吗
Detention, is it?
那我们就有大把时间去讨论
I guess we'll have plenty of time to discuss
你最爱的守护者黑伏都的命运了
the fate of your favorite Vindicator, Black Voodoo.
属于美国路易斯安那州新奥尔良街区
伏都教在新奥尔良很流行
法国区守护者总部的冠军
The champion of the French Quarter.
赌你不敢剧透
You wouldn't dare spoil the only thing
全世界唯一能带给我快乐的电影
that brings me joy in this world.
把你的假发给我
Give me your toupee.
什么假发
Toupee?
我可没戴假发
I don't wear a toupee.
那我们从波旁街说起吧
We fade in on Bourbon Street...
美国新奥尔良法国区一条著名古老街道
守护者联盟
史金纳校长  什么风把您吹来了
Principal Skinner. T-To what do we owe the honor, sir, at-
是你呀
Oh, it's just you.
这些东西哪来的
how'd you get all this stuff?
因为我说什么人们就做什么
'Cause people do whatever I say
否则我就剧透《守护者联盟》
or I spoil the Vindicators movie for them.
比如说
Like so:
让妈妈同意我用汽水泡麦片
tell Mom it's okay for me to have soda on my cereal.
我不确定  你妈不会答应的
I don't know. Mom's not gonna go for that.
好  那就准备好被剧透大结局吧
Okay. Get ready to hear the surprise ending.
让我猜猜  正义战胜了邪恶
Let me guess. The good guys win.
谁告诉你的
Who told you?
你没法给我剧透那电影
You can't spoil that movie for me,
因为我根本不在乎
because I don't care what happens.
作为一个成年人
You see, as a grown-up,
我早看透了穿着紧身服的超能力肌肉男们
I know that muscle jerks in tights with magic powers
拳打脚踢之后又深情拥抱
punching and hugging each other
都是哄小孩的瞎扯
is boring BS for babies.
剧透吧  告诉我摆设队长对拉链什么侠的
So go ahead, tell me what Captain Doodad does
做了什么
to Zippity whoever.
因为那根本没意义
Because it means nothing.
我的剧透力对你不起作用
My powers don't work on you.
但如果我能让剧透力为你服务呢
But what if I could make them work for you?
我喜欢这险恶的语气
Your sinister tone intrigues me.
今天的酒我请客
All-you-can-drink beers on me!
老谋子买单
But paid for by Moe.
我已经懒得表示惊讶了
All right, I'm not even gonna dignify that with a "Whaaa?"
上  小子
Do the thing, boy.
别  别 千万别剧透
No, no, don't ruin it, kid!
我还要等档期排到两元影院时
I'm taking my girlfriend to that movie
带我女朋友去看呢
when it gets to the two-dollar theater.
你昨晚几点回来的
What time did you get home last night?
这不能怪我
it's not my fault.
巴仔用他的剧透力给我带来太多酒水
Bart used his superpower to get me drunker than I've ever beer.
我担心这样勒索别人
I'm worried that all this blackmail
正在让巴仔学坏
is turning Bart into a bad person.
早上好啊  宝贝们
What's the story, morning glories?
巴仔  我不喜欢你用剧透的手段
Young man, I don't like the way you're using those spoilies
去指示别人
to boss people around.
哪有  我被赋予了一项超棒的能力
What? I was given an amazing power,
所以就用了呗
so I'm using it.
如果是你也会这么做的
If you were in my suitcase, you would do the same thing.
粉丝们深爱漫宝电影宇宙
Fans have a deep connection to the Marble Cinematic Universe.
我是不会利用这一点的  无论如何
I would never exploit that, not for anything.
是吗
Wouldn't you?
校园舞会
在星光里尬舞
春田小学
丽莎·辛普森  我想你的超能力
Lisa Simpson, I think your superpower
一定是偷心吧
must be stealing hearts.
你现在对利用的看法如何呢
How do you feel about exploitation now?
存在即合理吧
It's okay.
这场逗傻子的滑稽剧
How much longer do I have to keep up
我还得演多久
this kookaburra charade?
看你有多不想让你漫宝影业的老板们知道
How badly do you not want your bosses at Marble Studios
我利用了你这个醉肥仔看了那部电影了
to know that I used your drunken thumb to see that movie?
你把我当成你的"快乐流浪汉"了是吧
You think I'm your jolly swagman, do you?
此处引用了澳大利亚丛林民谣《丛林流浪》的歌词
没关系  我的小羊
Well, my jumbuck's gonna be free
《丛林民谣》讲述了一位快乐的流浪汉
在把一只偶遇的羊塞进旅行袋后
因遭到警察的追捕而投河自尽的故事
在下周四就能从你的旅行袋里解放出来了
from your tucker bag next Thursday,
等到那部电影登上每一张大银幕
when that movie goes wide on every screen in creation.
那之后  你就什么都不是了
And after that, you're nothing.
让我们继续嗨到派对结束吧
Let's get this party finished!
他说得对
He's right.
我快没时间了
I'm running out of time.
这是...终局之战了
This is... endgame!
生日快乐
老苏茜
今天我们迎来了我们最爱的橡树
And so, today, we celebrate the 200th birthday
老苏茜的200岁生日
of our beloved oak tree, Old Susie.
她庄严枝干所带来的阴凉惠泽我们镇上的婚礼
Her stately branches have shaded our town's weddings,
家庭聚会  以及那个...额...
family reunions, and quincen-- quincien--
墨西哥的女孩成人仪式
市长想说的词是Quinceañera
市长最终说出来的Bar Mitzvahs是犹太教的男孩成人仪式
墨西哥版的犹太成人礼
Mexican bar mitzvahs.
我们呢...
We're, uh, ow!
把耳朵捂住  是剧透男孩
Cover you ears! It's Spoiler Boy!
没错  就是我
That's right. It's me.
如果你们不想被剧透
And if you don't want the movie spoiled,
你们就得一起给我建一座
you'll all pull together and build me
我设计的梦中树屋
the ultimate tree house of my own design.
就在这老苏茜上
Right here in Old Susie.
不能建在老苏茜上啊
Not in Old Susie!
镇上的每个人都爱这棵树
Everyone in this town loves that tree!
我们没有选择
We have no choice.
我们都完完全全被他玩弄在鼓掌之中了
He's got us all by the short and curlies.
除非在这个孩子身上发生了一些不幸的意外
Unless the boy should meet with an unfortunate accident.
如果有任何可疑的事情发生在我身上
And if anything suspicious should happen to me,
我已经雇了镇上嗓门最大的人去每个街角
I've hired the loudest man in town to yell the ending
把电影结局吼出来了
on every street corner.
我准备好啦
I'm on it!
剧透
你们有24小时时间来建我的树屋
You have 24 hours to build my tree house.
时间可不等人哦
The clock is ticking.
伙计  你出院了
Hey, buddy. You're out of the hospital.
别跟我来这套
Don't you "Hey, buddy" me.
空射侠来看望的是我不是你
You stole my visit from Airshot.
你是反派
You-- you villain!
我是反派  怎么可能
Me, a villain? No way.
你勒索了全镇的人帮你造藏身之所
You just blackmailed the whole town to build you a lair.
好吧  我向你保证这件事
Okay. I will grant you the optics on the lair
进行得并不理想
are less than ideal.
你把力量都用在邪恶的事上
You have actual powers which you use for evil.
你是超级大反派
You're a supervillain!
竟敢叫我超级大反派
You dare call me a supervillain?
给我听好了
Then get a load of this:
全片最重要的剧透
the biggest spoiler in the whole movie!
镁镁侠
Magnesium Man!
不要继续说了
Don't say another word!
这会决定我们宇宙的命运
The fate of our universe depends on it.
这是哪
Where the hell am I?
放轻松  剧透小子
Relax there, Spoiler Boy.
我们只是把你从你的世界带到了我们的世界
All we did was take you from your dimension into ours.
漫宝宇宙
You know, the Marble universe?
你眼中的电影是我们眼中的现实
What you consider to be movies make up our reality.
不可能  超级英雄是假的
No way. Superheroes aren't real.
在你们眼里我这么蠢吗
How dumb do you think I am?
真正的超能力
Actual superpowers!
你在守护者电影里看到的
Everything you see in your Vindicator movies
都是真实发生的
actually happens to us.
彩蛋也是吗
Even the post-credit sequences?
我们带你来看看你自私行为导致的后果
We brought you here to see the result of your selfish actions.
空射侠  死了
Airshot! Dead?
可他在电影里活下来了
But in the movie he lives.
发生了什么
Wh-what happened?
都是因为你
You happened!
你个沼泽女巫娘养的
You son of a swamp witch!
你给那个漫画男看了
You showed your Comic Book Guy a spoiler
空射侠用口气拯救自己的剧透
of Airshot using his breath to save himself.
这个世界里的邪恶力量看到了这一幕
The powers of evil in our dimension
收到了警告  把他的嘴用胶带堵上了
saw this and, so warned, taped Airshot's mouth shut.
然后杀了他
And killed him.
我不知道会这样
I didn't know!
我从没想过剧透真的会伤害人
I never dreamed that spoilers really hurt people.
可那是真的  剧透会杀人
But they do. Spoilers kill!
我爱你  空射侠
I love you, Airshot!
虚拟现实起作用了
The virtual reality's working.
他完全不知道这些全是假的
The kid has no idea that this has all been fake.
不敢相信他竟然没注意到
I can't believe he didn't notice
他后院里的传送门
that the dimensional portal in his backyard
只是一个装满了荧光棒的垃圾袋
was just a garbage bag full of glow sticks.
告诉我这样做是对的
Tell me we're doing the right thing.
漫宝影业
来访人员
告诉我只有这样
Tell me this is Bart's best chance
巴仔才能成为一个好人
to choose to be a good person.
别担心  马姬
Don't worry, Marge.
这点装神弄鬼的小把戏伤害不了他的
No one's ever been hurt by a little gaslighting.
记得你总说的那句话吗
Remember how you always say that?
记得吗
Remember?
这可不是什么小把戏
Oh, don't think of it as gaslighting.
这是超级高端无敌酷炫的
Think of it as an ultra-enhanced,
沉浸式粉丝体验项目
immersive fan experience.
这么大费周章只为了防止剧透泄露
All this, just to keep spoilers from leaking.
守护者联盟  逗号 水晶战争 逗号 复活
Vindicators, colon, Crystal War, colon, Resurgence
如果票房失败
bombing at the box office
会产生毁灭性的后果
would have devastating consequences.
主题公园无人光顾  滞销的万圣节服装
Failing theme parks, unsold Halloween costumes
剧院爆米花  空射侠训练营
品牌口腔护理产品  守护者联盟系列电影  加油站杂货店前传故事
主题公园  守护者联盟广播网络  万圣节服装
堆积如山
rotting on the docks,
爆米花农民相继自杀
mass suicides by popcorn farmers;
在第二个周末  票房占有率
anything worse than a 55% hold
不到百分之55的电影
on its second weekend,
全球经济像纸牌屋一样瞬间崩塌
the global economy collapses like a house of cards.
这是你想看到的吗  小姑娘  是吗
Is that what you want, little girl? Is it?
不  不是
No. No.
巴仔已经知道错了
Bart clearly feels bad.
能把他放出来吗
Can't we let him out now?
还不行  我们要做到百分百确定
No. We have to be absolutely sure.
提高模拟强度
Increasing simulation intensity.
把他带过来
Bring me the boy.
记着  孩子  别剧透
Remember, kid, no spoilers!
我们宇宙的命运在此一举
Our universe depends on it!
也别盗版电影  这样伤人又伤己
And don't pirate movies. That hurts everyone.
你就是知晓结局的男孩
So, the boy who's seen how all this ends.
把你知道的告诉我
Tell me what you know,
这样我就可以彻底毁灭守护者联盟
so I can use it to destroy the Vindicators.
作为回报  我可以满足你内心深处的渴望
In return, I will grant your deepest desire:
真正的超能力
actual superpowers.
肌肉
Muscles...
钢爪
claws...
摩托
bike!
真正的超能力
Real powers.
这可比剧透能力还厉害
That's even better than spoiler powers.
不好  儿子要选择成为坏人了
Oh, no. Our son is going to choose evil.
完蛋了  儿子太傻  要被反派迷惑了
Oh, no! Our son is so stupid he's going to fall for this!
不管这是不是真实的
It doesn't matter that's it not real.
巴仔的灵魂已经岌岌可危
Bart's soul is at stake.
多真挚的感情  咱俩的赌注该加码了吧
Great emotion. Talk about upping the ante.
把剧透告诉我  孩子
Tell me the spoilers, child.
拥抱你成为反派的命运吧
And embrace your destiny as a villain.
空射侠
Airshot.
好吧  我来告诉你怎么做才能获胜
All right. I'll tell you what you have to do to win.
-不要  -这可不好  孩子
- No! - Uh-uh, kid.
你想得美
Eat my shorts.
不要
No. No.
不要啊
No...!
我们的儿子是个好人  是好人
Our son's a good guy! A good guy.
但他还是很傻  太傻了
But he's still stupid. So stupid...
这孩子拒绝了真正的超能力
The kid turned down actual superpowers.
我想他应该不会再剧透了
I think he'll keep his mouth shut.
好  那就饶他一命吧
Okay. We'll let him live.
暂且放过他
For now.
我回来了
I'm back.
希望还来得及
I just hope it's not too late.
今天几号了
What day is it?
怎么了  是烈士纪念日前一周的周三
Why, it's the Wednesday before Memorial Day, it is.
那还有时间
Then there's still time.
电影没有被剧透
The movie hasn't been spoiled.
别担心  儿子
Don't worry, son.
我依然保守着你不为人知的秘密
Your secret I forgot is safe with me.
我拯救了他们  我不是反派
I saved their universe. I'm not a villain.
我是个超级英雄
I'm a superhero.
-什么时候告诉他实话  -永远别说
- When can we tell him? - Never.
好了  谁也不会剧透的
All right. No one's gonna talk.
电影安全了
The movie's safe.
暂且放他们一马
We'll let them live. For now.
已启动
已解除
优选公爵的汽车美容
我不是坏人
I'm not a bad guy.
我是个好人
I'm a good guy.
我再也不会剧透了
I'll never spoil anything again.
我已经改过自新了  改过自新
I'm a changed boy. A changed boy.
把我摆在漫画书和棒球卡旁边
我早就看出来你有做英雄的潜质
I always knew you had the stuff of heroes.
告诉我  白鲸侠有没有夺回
Just tell me, does Moby Man take his place
他应得的鱼多维亚王位
as the rightful sovereign of Fishtonia?
有没有  巴仔  快告诉我
Does he? Bart! Tell me!
大家停下吧
Stop your labors, good folk.
镁镁侠保佑我们每一个人
Magnesium Man bless us, every one.
巴仔言而有信
And Bart was as good as his word.
绝不剧透
He kept his mouth shut.
《守护者联盟2  水晶战争  复活》
等到首映的那一天
So when everyone finally saw the movie on opening day,
大家满心欢喜地看完了电影
they were filled with joy.
然后马上用手机
Then immediately got on their phones
把剧透发到社交媒体上
and spoiled it for everyone else.